Finding Aid for the Ralph Edwards Productions Production Records PASC.0336
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Truth or Consequences, 1940-1988; Series 2.
  - Scripts and Production Materials, Subseries 1.
    - Program no. 1352 (Master Script and Research), 1962 March 19 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: KNOCK KNOCK GIFTS BUILDUP (Bobby Lauher) & PAYOFF > BOBBO BACKGROUND GUESSERS BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/3/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1353 (Master Script and Research), 1962 March 20 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: K.P. POTATOES MODEL BUILDUP & PAYOFF > JACKHAMMER PIGEON REMOTE BUILDUP (Milt Larsen) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/4/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1354 (Master Script and Research), 1962 March 20 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: LAUGH IT UP SONGS > BOBBO'S BOX > BACKSTAGE TURNTABLE KID FRAME BUILDUP (Jerry Payne) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/5/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1355 (Master Script and Research), 1962 April 2 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: WHY MAJOR TIMERS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > COVER GIRL HALLWAY BUILDUP (MODEL DOLORES FAITH) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/6/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1356 (Master Script and Research), 1962 April 2 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: HIDDEN AMBITION INTUITION BUILDUP & PAYOFF > INSTRUMENTAL PLAYERS BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/9/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1357 (Master Script and Research), 1962 April 3 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: STAR IMITATION REUNION BUILDUP (Day, Dennis)& PAYOFF > SEPARATE FIGHT FRAME REMOTE BUILDUP (Bobby Lauher, Jerry Payne) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/10/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1358 (Master Script and Research), 1962 April 3 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: WIN YOUR EASTER BONNET BUILDUP (celebrity: Stevens, Inger) & PAYOFF > ROME ADVENTURE CROSS COUNTRY CARRYOVER BUILDUP (contestants: Kennedy, Jim & Martha) ( Tory Donahue Plugs Warner Bros movie "ROME ADVENTURE" starring TROY DONAHUE)
      Air date: 4/11/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1359 (Master Script and Research), 1962 April 8 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: POP UP PASSERS > CROSS COUNTRY REPORT & MAIL PLUG #1 > GENII WISH FRUSTRATION BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/12/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1360 (Master Script and Research), 1962 April 8 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: CLIP HUBBY TIE FRAME (Milt Larsen ) > CROSS COUNTRY REPORT & MAIL PLUG #2 > HALLWAY MONITOR REUNION BUILDUP (contestant: White, Mrs. Grace) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/13/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1361 (Master Script and Research), 1962 April 9 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: CATCH SNEAKY HUSBAND > CROSS COUNTRY REPORT & MAIL PLUG #3 > JANOS QUESTIONS BUILDUP (Janos rohaska) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 4/16/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1362, 1962 April 9 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: STUNT SALARY HUBBIES > CROSS COUNTRY REPORT & MAIL PLUG #4 > WISHING WELL MATCHERS BUILDUP & PAYOFF Includes master script and research notes.
      Air date: 4/17/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1363, 1962 April 14 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. PRE-EMPTED; aired as NBC 1373 (5/2/62) Includes master script and research notes.
      Scheduled air date: 4/18/1962. For contents see program no. 1373. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1364, 1962 April 14 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: GLAMOUR WIG WIFE SURPRISE > CROSS COUNTRY REPORT & MAIL PLUG #5 > HAUNTED DOLLHOUSE REUNION BUILDUP & PAYOFF Includes master script and research notes.
      Air date: 4/19/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1365, 1962 April 15 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: WILSON VANISHING WIFE BUILDUP (Magician Mark Wilson & wife Donni Darnell assists in act) & PAYOFF > CROSS COUNTRY REPORT & MAIL PLUG #6 > BURRO PROSPECTORS PARKING LOT BUILDUP & PAYOFF Includes master script and research notes.
      Air date: 4/20/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1366, 1962 April 15 (Box 5)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: PHYSICAL FITNESS BETTORS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > CROSS COUNTRY REPORT & MAIL PLUG #7 > BET ON BOYS HALLWAY BUILDUP & PAYOFF Includes master script and research notes.
      Air date: 4/23/1962. Television broadcast.
    - Program nos. 1382-1486, 1973 June 19-1974 June 15; scripts (Box 250)
    - program no. 1414. (Box 5)
    - Program nos. 1415-1512, 1962 June 12-October 29 (Box 6)
      Host: Bob Barker. Includes master scripts and research notes.
    - Program nos. 1488-1586, 1974 May 16-June 26; scripts (Box 251)
    - Program nos. 1513-1595 (Master Scripts and Research), 1962 October 30-1963 February 27 (Box 7)
    - Program nos. 1587-1601, 1974 September 24-October 8; scripts (Box 252)
    - Program nos. 1596-1615, 1963 February 27-March 26 (Box 35)
    - Program nos. 1602-1717, 1974 October 9-1975 March 19; scripts (Box 253)
      Annotated Metro Media television broadcast script.
    - Program nos. 1615-1755 Acts, 1974 October 31-1975 May 18 (Box 237)
      Written by Paul Edwards.
    - Program nos. 1616-1698, 1963 March 26-July 23 (Box 36)
    - Program nos. 1699-1778, 1963 July 23-November 6 (Box 37)
    - Program nos. 1718-1754, 1975 March 25-May 8; scripts (Box 254)
    - Program nos. 1779-1859, 1963 November 11-1964 March 3 (Box 38)
    - Program nos. 1860-1936, 1964 March 3-June 10 (Box 39)
    - Program nos. 1937-2024, 1964 June 15-October 20 (Box 40)
    - Program nos. 2025-2104, 1964 October 21-1965 February 10 (Box 41)
    - Program nos. 2105-2144, 1965 February 10-April 6; scripts (Box 42)
    - Program nos. 2145-2191, 1965 April 6-June 7; scripts (Box 64)
    - Program nos. 2176-2259, 1965 May 31-1965 September 11 (Box 42)
      Host: Bob Barker. Show run-downs.
    - Program nos. 2192-2240, 1965 June 7-August 16; scripts (Box 59)
    - Program nos. 2241-2259, 1965 August 30-September 24 (Box 58)
      Scripts. Host: Bob Barker.
  - Business Papers, Subseries 2.
    - 1980s Show Revival Papers (Box 307, Folder 1)
      Includes clippings and memos regarding the revival of the program.
    - 25th Anniversary, 3 folders (Box 238)
    - Al Paschall Business Card (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Al Simon Papers, 1 folder (Box 237)
      Business files of staff member, Al Simon.
    - Assorted Business Notes, 1965; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Assorted Business Papers, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Assorted Business Papers, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Assorted Papers, 2 folders (Box 232)
      Folders marked, "Misc."
    - Bob Barker Biographical Notes, 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Bob Barker Press Lunch Notes, 1970 April 1; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Broadcast Notes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 238)
      Consists of notes on radio broadcasts including information regarding the condition of the sound recording; distinguishing event of the program; points of interest; consequences; good acts; good questions, and notes on the overall appeal of the show.
    - California Alumni Association Benefit, 1961; 1 folder (Box 238)
      Papers documenting a benefit performance.
    - Clippings, 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Clippings, 2 folders (Box 238)
    - Clippings, 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Ed Bailey Release and Compliance Reports, 1964 November (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Fred Carney Information (Box 297, Folder 2)
      Show production manager.
    - Hanna Center for Boys Show Participation Agreement, 1951; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Interoffice Memos, 2 folders (Box 232)
    - Interview with Fred Carney, Production Manager (Box 237)
    - Jack Bailey Biographical File, 1954; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Letterhead (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - List of Hosts, 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Live Presentations Promotional Materials, 1980; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - March of Dimes Sound Recording Documentation, 1955 January 18 (Box 238)
      Letter to station managers regarding a special promotional sound recording made to raise funds for the March of Dimes.
    - Market Sales, 1976; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Medical Service Society of America, Memphis Chapter, Student Nurse Scholarship Fund Sponsorship (Box 307, Folder 3)
      Sponsorship brochure.
    - Miss Hush Clippings (Box 233)
      Clippings regarding a song used on the program.
    - Miss Hush Papers, 2 folders (Box 238)
    - Miss Moppet Clippings, 1965; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Mr. Nemesis Contest Press Releases, 1 folder (Box 237)
    - New Television Technique (Box 301, Folder 1)
      Description of how Ralph Edwards developed a new technique of filming television shows.
    - New Television Technique (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - New Truth or Consequences and Truth or Consequences Junior, 1 folder (Box 238)
      Notes on changes made to the shows.
    - New Truth or Consequences Notes, 1977; 2 folders (Box 238)
    - New Truth or Consequences, 1992; 1 folder (Box 238)
      Bob Chadwick proposal.
    - New Truth or Consequences, 1993; 1 folder (Box 238)
      Notes for Ralph Edwards.
    - Notes on Improvements to the Show, 1987; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Personnell Directory (Box 232)
      Includes contact information for employees of the Biow Company and the Philip Morris Company.
    - Pilot Show Scripts and Memos, Sales Presentation Papers, 1977 February 10 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Press Packet, 1 folder (Box 238)
      Includes photographs and slides.
    - Press Release for "The Best of Truth or Consequences", 1993; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Press Releases, 1958; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Press Releases, 1960; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Press Releases, 1960; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Press Releases, 1961; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Promo Disclosures, 1877-1978 (Box 302)
    - Publicity Packet, 1977; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Publicity Packet (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - Publicity Packets (Box 233)
    - Publicity Program (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Radio Station List, 1 folder (Box 238)
      Radio stations that broadcast the program.
    - Ralph Edwards's Notes, 1977; 1 folder (Box 237)
      Ralph Edwards's notes on acts and shows.
    - Ratings Reports, 1961-1965; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Remember Me Memorandum, 1974 March 18 (Box 237)
    - Roadshow Miami Itinerary, 1982 March 27-April 4; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Roadshow Publicity (Box 237)
    - Sales Presentation Notes, 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Sales Presentation Script, 1977 Feburary 10 (Box 237)
    - Sponsor Magazine Article (Box 297, Folder 2)
      Show is named, "Program of the Year."
    - Television Station List, 1955 February 16; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Truth or Consequences Fiesta Schedule, 1990 (Box 237)
    - Truth or Consequences, NM Celebration Papers, 1952 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - War Bond Tours Paperwork, 1 folder (Box 233)
    - War Bond Tours Statistics, 1942-1945; 1 folder (Box 237)
      List of cities program was played for War Bond purchase along with amounts of bonds sold.
    - Wickel Park Papers, 1 folder (Box 237)
  - Correspondence, Subseries 3.
    - Al Paschal Letter (Box 306, Folder 3)
      Regarding the sale of War Bonds in Cincinnati.
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1945-1950; 1 folder (Box 238)
    - Assorted Correspondence, 1948-1953 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 303, Folder 6)
      Also includes clippings, list of consequences.
    - Correspondence with Don Martin, 1983; 1 folder (Box 237)
      Regarding production of the program at the Music Hall in Seattle.
    - Financial Correspondence, 1950; 1 folder (Box 232)
    - General Correspondence, 1959; 2 folders (Box 238)
    - KXOA Correspondence, 1954 February (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Proctor and Gamble Correspondence, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Proctor and Gamble Correspondence, 1958-1959; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Requests for Copies of Broadcasts, 2 folders (Box 233)
    - Requests for Copies of Videotapes, 1989; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - To Dick Currier of Consolidated Film Industries, 1951; 1 folder (Box 232)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Subseries 4.
    - Assorted Negatives, 1950-1964; negatives (Box 314)
    - Assorted Negatives, ne (Box 315)
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 315)
    - Assorted Negatives, 1944-1969; negatives (Box 316)
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 317)
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 319)
    - Assorted Photographs (Box 46)
    - Bob Hilton Photographs, 1977; slides, negatives, prints, contact sheets (Box 46)
      Publicity shots.
    - Grand Canyon (Box 295, Folder 4)
      Photographs and notes on the placing of the Truth or Consequences mileage sign at the bottom of the Grand Canyon.
    - Negatives (Program nos. 00-21) (Radio), 1949 January 20-1951 January 25; negatives (Box 196)
      Ralph Edwards, host.
    - Negatives (Program nos. 645-676) (Radio), 1947 June 28-1948 March 13; negatives (Box 203)
    - Negatives (Program nos. 601-644) (Radio), 1947 January 25-June 21; negatives (Box 206)
    - Negatives (Program nos. 677-699) (Radio), 1948 March 20-October 16; negatives (Box 207)
    - Negatives (Program nos. 755-805) (Radio), 1950 January 7-1951 February 27; negatives (Box 197)
      Host, Ralph Edwards.
    - Negatives (Program nos. 700-754) (Radio), 1948 October 23-1949 December 31; negatives (Box 204)
    - Negatives (program nos. 807-911) (Radio), 1951 March 13-1954 April 8; negatives (Box 195)
    - Photograph Captions, 1943 (Box 193)
    - Photographs (Box 56)
    - Photographs (Radio), 1951 March 7-1954 February 11; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 193)
    - Photographs (Radio), 1951 March 13-1954 March 25; photographs (Box 193)
    - Program nos. 1-66 (Negatives), 1954 May 18-1955 August 16; negatives (Box 188)
      Jack Bailey, host. Television broadcast.
    - Program nos. 67-90 (Negatives), 1955 August 23-1956 February 3; negatives (Box 189)
    - Program nos. 91-121 (Negatives), 1956 February 10-September 7; negatives (Box 187)
    - Public Relations and Unidentified Photograph Negatives (Box 208)
    - Steve Dunne Program nos. 1-25 (Negatives), 1957 December 12-1958 May 30; negatives (Box 195)
      Steve Dunne, host. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1 (Photographs), 1977 July 23; prints, slides, negatives, proofs (Box 46)
      Host: Bob Hilton.
    - Program no. 2 (Photographs), 1977 July 23; photographs, negatives (Box 46)
      Publicity shots of Bob Hilton and Ralph Edwards.
    - Program no. 2 (Photographs), 1977 July 23; photographs (Box 46)
      Host: Bob Hilton. Celebrity guest: Lassie.
    - Program no. 2 (Photographs), 1977 July 23; photographs, negatives, slides, contact sheets (Box 46)
    - Program nos. 12-247 (Negatives), 1940 June 8-1942 December 26; negatives (Box 99)
    - Program nos. 12-339 (Photographs), 1940 June 8-1944 January 8 (Box 77)
    - Program no. 14 (Photographs), 1977 August 7; photographs, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      Host: Bob Hilton. Dodger Stadium consequence with Dodger pitcher, Tommy John.
    - Program no. 18 (Photographs), 1957 May 24 (Box 94)
    - Program no. 26 (Photographs), 1977 September 25; photograph (Box 46)
      Host: Bob Hilton. Guest: H. Tobin Groves. Model: Marlene Amy.
    - Program nos. 105-813 (Photographs), 1957 May 24-1960 March 9 (Box 94)
    - Program nos. 248-329 (Negatives), 1942 December 26-1943 December 4; negatives (Box 98)
    - Program nos. 331-419 (Negatives), 1943 December 11-1944 December 12; negatives (Box 100)
    - Program nos. 341-523 (Photographs), 1944 January 15-1946 February 23 (Box 78)
    - Program nos. 420-469 (Negatives), 1944 December 23-1945 June 10 (Box 97)
    - Program nos. 474-511 (Negatives), negatives (Box 105)
    - Program nos. 474-511 (Negatives), 1945 July 7-1946 January 5; negatives (Box 105)
    - Program nos. 512-524 (Negatives), 1946 January 12-March 30; negatives (Box 104)
    - Program nos. 523-641 (Photographs), 1946 February 23-1947 June 14 (Box 79)
    - Program nos. 565-600 (Negatives), 1946 September 21-1947 January 20; negatives (Box 103)
    - Program nos. 643-755 (Photographs), 1947 June 21-1950 January 7 (Box 80)
      Celebrity guests: William Demarest; Dorothy Lamour; Ned Sparks; Paul Frees; Martha Graham; Jack Benny; Jack Dempsey.
    - Program nos. 755-804 (Photographs), 1950 January 7-1951 February 20 (Box 94)
    - Program nos. 813-1182 (Photographs), 1960 March 9-1961 August 8; photographs (Box 96)
    - Program nos. 1184-1419, 1961 August 10-1962 July 5; photographs (Box 96)
    - Program nos. 1282-1385, 1961 December 14-1962 May 18; negatives (Box 84)
    - Program nos. 1419-1712, 1962 July 5-1963 August 20; photographs (Box 95)
    - Program nos. 1713-2218, 1963 August 21-1965 July 28; photographs (Box 101)
    - Program nos. 1713-2230, 1963 August 21-1965 August 13; photographs (Box 101)
  - Clippings & Ephemera, Subseries 5.
    - Al Stovall's Restaurant Menu, Truth or Consequences New Mexico (Box 306, Folder 7)
      Souvenir menu postcard.
    - Article on the Show in KFYR Dailies, 1952 February (Box 306, Folder 7)
      Photograph of Ralph Edwards on cover.
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 310)
    - Assorted Clippings, 1964-1969 (Box 311)
      Includes Bob Barker clippings.
    - Assorted Clippings, 1965,1967-1968 (Box 312)
      Includes: 1965 anniversary clippings; Bob Barker clippings.
    - Assorted Newspaper Clippings (Box 309)
    - Clippings, 1969 August-December (Box 310)
    - Contestant Visits Omaha, 1948 August 1 (Box 306, Folder 3)
      Article in Wow News Tower.
    - Fiesta Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box 307)
    - Guideposts Article on Ralph Edwards's Skill at Creating Consequences, 1952 (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Lebanon Daily News Clipping, 1948 September 2 (Box 307, Folder 5)
      Front page photograph article
    - Miss Hush Clippings, 4 folders (Box 310)
    - Nostalgia Digest Ralph Edwards Cover Story, 2001 October (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - They Take the Consequences, 1942 May 2 (Box 303, Folder 3)
      Liberty Magazine article by Ralph Edwards
    - Truth or Consequences Trouble Shooter, 1945 October (Box 303, Folder 3)
      Radio Life article on assorted consequences.
    - Walking Man and Miss Hush Clippings and Papers (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - Walking Man Contest Clippings (Box 306, Folder 1)
      Special contest to benefit the American Heart Association.
    - Walking Man Contest Clippings (Box 309)
    - War Bond Show Ticket (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - War Bond Show Ticket; Response to Request for Show Tickets (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - War Bonds Poster (Box 307, Folder 6)
  - Games, Subseries 6.
    - Bingo Cards and Party Book (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - Cover of Home Audio Recording Game (Box 307)
  - Sound Recordings, Subseries 7.
    - Act Sound Recordings, 1940 May 11-1951 May 29; cassette tapes (Box 321)
      15 audio cassettes. Contents: J.L. Rayward (5/11/40) -- 1st NBC broadcast (8/17/40) -- Clear Throat (5/31/41) -- Hellzapoppin (7/19/41) -- First Anniversary (8/16/41) - Elephant no. 2 (9/20/41) -- Sammy Kaye (11/8/41) -- Hammer/Cind. no. 1 (2/14/42) -- Cinderella no.s 2 (2/28/42) -- Visit From Mom (3/21/42) -- Knives (5/2/42) -- Mind Reader no.2 (5/22/43) - Returned Sailor (9/11/43) -- Guadalcanal (11/6/43) -- Thump Melons (11/2/43) -- Fred Allen (3/4/44) -- Bill Bendix (10/20/45) -- Home for Xmas (12/22/45) -- Crackpot no. 5 (/126/46) -- Helicopter Love ($/5/47) -- Jack Dempsey (1/3/48) -- Dunk Husband (2/28/48) -- John Wayne (5/7/49) -- C.K. Mind Reader (5/21/49) -- Wife/Sol. Tele. (6/18/49) -- Re-Enact Thanks (11/19/49 -- Seal Bed Street (5/20/50) -- Retired Teacher (6/3/50 -- Ronald Reagan (5/15/51) -- Soldier Clerk (5/29/51).
    - Ronald Reagan Act, streaming audio
      Program no. 748.
    - Ronald Reagan Act, streaming audio
      Program no. 816.
    - The Ballad of Truth or Consequences New Mexico, 1964 March 5; streaming audio
      Sung by Jack Smith. Duration: 1:41. Written by BUDDY PEPPER & FRANK M. CHAPMAN.
- The Cross-Wits, 1975-1980; Series 3.
  Comedy game. Two three-member teams, each comprised of two celebrities and one non-celebrity captain, take turns solving a crossword puzzle with comedy clues provided by the host. Filled-in words within the puzzle provide clues to the name of a mystery person, place or thing. First team to guess the mystery name wins. Host: Jack Clark. Announcers at different times during the seven-year run: John Harlan; Jerry Bishop, and Jay Stewart. Model, Jerri Fiala.
  - Celebrity Guest Lists, 1979-1980 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and Slides (Box 52)
  - Photographs and Slides (Box 53)
  - Playback Schedules, 1975-1980; 1 red binder (Box 299)
    Includes: air dates; show numbers; celebrity players; contestants and recording dates.
  - Production Files (Box 290)
    For show nos. 42,61,195,199,682,684,688.
  - Puzzles, 1975-1977 (Box 45)
  - Puzzles (Box 47)
  - Puzzles (nos. 1-699) (Box 49)
  - Rules, Press Releases (Box 49)
  - Show Tickets (Box 306, Folder 7)
- End of the Rainbow, 1957-1958; Series 4.
  On this show Bob Barker and co-host Art Baker went out to various places in America and surprised the less-fortunate who helped others when they could barely help themselves.
  - Art Baker Photographs (Box 56)
  - Negatives (Box 126)
  - Promotional Materials (Box 56)
  - Publicity (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - Scripts, 1958 (Box 290)
    Scripts for program nos. 1 and 6.
  - Scripts and Production Files (shows 1-6), 1957 December 4-1958 February 15 (Box 52)
- Funny Boners, 1954-1955; Series 5.
  Funny Boners was a children's version of the nighttime game show Truth or Consequences, both of which were developed by executive producer Ralph Edwards. The show was hosted by ventriloquist Jimmy Weldon and his dummies Webster Webfoot, a bragging duck, and Easy Marvin. If a contestant answered a question incorrectly, he or she would have to pay the consequences by performing an embarrassing stunt.
  - Photographs and Negatives (Box 56)
  - Scripts and Production Materials, 1954 November 20-1955 June 22 (Box 50)
- Knockout, 1977-1978; Series 7.
  This game show format pitted three contestants against each other to identify which of four listed items was out of place. The show was created by Mark Maxwell-Smith, hosted by Arte Johnson and announced by Jay Stewart. The format was successfully revamped by the BBC as Odd One Out in 1983. Aired on NBC tv 5 times per week.
  - Airdates, 1977; 1 yellow binder (Box 299)
    Includes air dates, tape dates, show numbers, contestant names, prizes.
  - Assorted Materials, 1977-1979 (Box 298, Folder 2)
    Includes: slides; scripts; production information; rules and regulations, and contestant list.
  - Cards (Box 50)
  - Graphics (Box 50)
  - Last Show Releases (Box 50)
  - Photographs and Slides, 1977 July 29 (Box 56)
  - Pilot Script and Production Materials, 1977 (Box 298)
    Includes two versions of the pilot script and notes on show sound effects, music cues and electronic devices.
  - Production Files (Box 290)
    For show nos. 6,17,27,36,37,138,142.
  - Rules (Box 50)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1977 September 12 (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - Script and Cards (Box 49)
  - Vizmo Graphics (Box 49)
- Name That Tune, Series 8.
  Musical game. Two contestants vied for cash and prizes through a series of competitions that tested the player's ability to identify song titles correctly. Games were: Pick a Tune; The Golden Medley, and Bid a Note. Later version had a $100,000 jackpot, the largest at the time. Syndicated show was hosted by Tom Kennedy, the daytime show on NBC was hoted by Dennis James. Announcer: Jack Harlan. Kathie Lee Johnson (later Kathie Lee Gifford) and Steve Marsh sang.
  - Publicity, Subseries 1.
    - Press Kits (Box 50)
    - Press Kits (Box 51)
  - Production Files, Subseries 2.
    - Production Files (Box 55)
      Includes cue sheets, music clearance information, scripts, etc.
    - Production Files (Box 290)
      For show nos. pilot, 3,28,31,93,277.
    - Production Information (Box 102)